我要再看一眼.有人反对吗?
I wanna take another look.Anyone object?
不不,看吧,请便
No,go ahead.Be my guest.
- 我从来没有见过那么多的钱 - 主啊
- I've never seen that much money. - Mercy.
看看这些.真是太夸张了
Look at that.That is awesome.
- 你觉得这里有多少? - 我不知道.几千吧
- How much do you think there is? - I don't know.Thousands.
好了
All right.
我还是觉得我们应该交给警察
I still say we should take it to the police.
等等,好吗.听我把话说完,行不?我们中的一个拿着这
Hold on,all right.Just hear me out,okay?One of us holds it.
我们保留,大概,我不知道,30天
We check in,say,I don't know,30 days...
如果没有人来报告丢失,我们就三个人平分了
if nobody's reported it missing,then we split it between us.
是啊.好吧,就这样
Yeah.All right.Okay.
那么,谁来拿着?
So,who holds it?
- 我不介意 - 不
- I wouldn't mind. - No.
不,因为我都不认识你 我也不认识他
No,'cause I don't know you,and I don't know him.
我怎么能够假定你们不会消失?
How am I supposed to know you won't disappear?
是啊,他说到重点了
Yeah,he has got a point.
如果是我们在这里,他来照管呢?
What about if our man here,he looks after it?
为了证明他不是个小偷,我并不是说你就是...
But to prove he's not a thief,I'm not saying that you are...
他可以去银行.这太聪明了
he goes to the bank.This is brilliant.
取出...你有多少?
Take out...What you got?
我的社保账户里面有6000镑
I've got 6,000 in the building society.
你有6000镑,好,那就拿出来6000 给我们每人3000
You've got 6,000,okay.Takes out 6,000.Gives us 3,000 each.
- 而我则拿着箱子 - 当然
- But I keep the case? - Obviously.
我没什么问题
I ain't got a problem with that.
如果一个月内你都没有听到任何事情 我们就回来,一起分这个钱
If you don't hear anything in a month,we'll come back.Split the money.
- 好吧 - 是吧?好了,就这样吧
- Okay. - Yeah?Okay.Let's do it.
伙计,我们要发财了 我都不能相信
Man,we're gonna be so rich.I can't believe it.
今天早上我出来的时候,口袋里面就只有20镑
I came out this morning,I had 20 quid in my pocket.
而现在,我就能分到25000镑的三分之一了
Now,I'm looking at a third share in 25,000.
从天而降,碰巧就被我们找到了
It's like it just came out of the sky and we just found it there.
天堂的礼物啊
Brought from heaven,or something.
现在情况如何,Danny?
How's it going,Danny?
- 什么? - 比分
- What? - The score.
如果以1-10分来评判,你觉得有多少分?
How do you think it's going on a scale of 1 to 10?
或许9分?
A nine maybe?
9分左右
Nine-ish.
- 没有吗? - 问你的问题
- No? - Ask your question.
你怎么知道这个箱子里面有多少钱?
How do you know how much is in the case?
我们还没有数吗?
We didn't count it yet?
妈的
Shit.
- 怎么了? - 他做的好事.走吧
- What happened? - He did.Come on.
本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子 字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第1季第2集
S01E02 Faking It
扑克千术的首要规则:
First rule of cheating at cards:
永远掩饰好你的动作
Always cover the move.
说错了.大动作掩护小动作
Misdirection.Big movement covers the small.
很简单的规则
Simple stuff.
还有,如果你可以的话,永远坐在门边
And,if you can,always sit by the door.
- 瞧,Mick - 算了吧
- Look,Mick. - Forget it.
不,我没有打算就此算了,好吗?好吧,我搞砸了
No,I don't want to forget it.All right?Okay,I screwed up.
是啊,你学到了什么?一句话来概括
Yeah,what did you learn?In a sentence.
按照预定的计划来做
Do it by the book.
这边走
This way.
你又搞砸了,Danny 我要把它刺在你的屁股上
You screw up again,Danny,I'll have it tattooed on your ass.
- 这个Frank Gorley是谁? - 魔鬼
- So who's this Frank Gorley? - Beelzebub.
我觉得我们可以以其人之道还治其人之身
I say we give him a taste of his own medicine.
我认识一些人
I know some people.
我可以以人头担保他们能以 任意一种方法来害你
I can personally vouch for how many places they can hurt you.
- 那不是我们要做的 - 那我们要做什么?
- That's not what we do. - What are we gonna do,then?
Ash?
他在伦敦西区经营了一家旅馆和赌场
He runs a hotel and casino in the West End.
赌场是他的爱好
The casino's bent.
有人从东欧运送姑娘到他旅馆中
He ships in girls from Eastern Europe for the hotel.
那些船家在赌桌上输掉了他们的钱 只能从匈牙利带姑娘过来
Punters lose their money on the tables,then curl up with Hilda from Hungary.
他不是那种你可以随便对付的人
Not the sort of man you take liberties with.
事实上,如果我们有一份不要去的地方的列表...
In fact,if we had a list of places not to go...
他会列在最上面
he'd be right there at the top.
帮我找出个入口
Find me an in.
和以前一样
The usual.
我就差这一张牌就能成千王之王
I was one card short of a great hand.
或许我应该对你进行宵禁令
Maybe I should put you on a curfew.
你可以试试看啊
I'd like to see you try.
- 你不再是20岁的人了,Albert - 我就是
- You're not 20 years old anymore,Albert. - Yes,I am.
这里,就是这么认为的
Up here,where it counts.
- 你建立了一个非常不好的榜样 - 好吧
- You are setting a very bad example. - Good.
我听说你对小Danny很不好
I hear you're giving young Danny a hard time.
他搞砸了
He screwed up.
我们都搞砸了
We all screw up.
- 所以你接下来才会要考虑作什么 - 或许吧
- It's what you do next that counts. - Maybe.
他有诈骗的天分.你是教不了的
He's got grift sense.You can't teach that.
而且我不会永远在你旁边,你会需要他的
And I'm not gonna be around forever,so you'll need him.
让我来担心Danny吧.你好好休息一下
Let me worry about Danny.You just get some rest.
我们晚一些打电话给你
We'll call back later.
你还需要什么吗,Albie?
Is there anything you want,Albie?
3个护士和一桌的牌
Three nurses and a deck of cards.
我们要回旅馆和Ash碰面.看他找到了什么
We'll meet Ash back at the hotel.See what he's got.
等等
Wait.
给我打电话
Call me.
- Peter? - 什么事?
- Peter? - Yes?
Maureen Phillips,媒体服务的
Maureen Phillips,media services.
- 媒体? - 不好意思.你好
- Media? - Sorry.Hello.
我已经在做了
I'm already on it.
请告诉部长,一切都在掌握之中 他没有什么好担心的
Please tell the Minister it's all in hand.He has nothing to worry about.
我现在就和Peter在一起
I'm with Peter now.
是的
Yeah.
我回去的路上会打电话给你.好的
I'll call you as soon as I'm on my way back.Okay.
对不起.你知道那些政客的嘴脸
Sorry about that.You know what politicians are like.
是啊
Yes.
事情是这样的,有人对我们泄漏说...
The thing is,we've been tipped off...
新闻局正在深入英国国民健康服务进行调查
that the press are conducting an investigation into NHS Trust services.
- 而这家医院被打上了记号 - 我明白了
- And this hospital's been earmarked. - I see.
他们会选择一个病人并在 整个过程中跟踪他的情况...
They select a patient and follow his progress through the system...
并随时进行报告,直到他离开
debriefing him as and when he leaves.
这件事情...
Well,the thing is...
他们选的那个病人是个老头儿...
The patient they've selected is an elderly man...
叫Albert Stroller?
called Albert Stroller?
上帝,我现在似乎就能看到报纸的标题了
God,I can just see the headlines now.
好的,瞧,我会马上着手...
Right,look,I'll get onto it...
找到他,Peter,像对待王子般对待他
Find him,Peter,treat him like a prince.
我们现在可都靠你了
We're all in your hands,now.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果我们一旦需要Albert...
If ever we needed Albert...
即使有入口,我也找不到
If there is an in,I can't find it.
瞧,我们知道他玩牌
Well,look,we know he plays cards.
我们也知道他能发现千术
We also know he can spot a cheat.
女人?
Women?
他有两打妓女可以随时使用,24除以7 但从来没有靠近过她们
He's got two dozen hookers on tap,24/7,but doesn't go near them.
我跟赌场的某个管理人员聊了一会儿.这个家伙很不合群
I spoke to one of the croupiers at the casino.The guy's a loner.
他每天晚上都把自己锁在房间里面
He locks himself in his room every night.
- 没有朋友? - 没有,什么也没有
- No friends? - No,nothing.
- 亲戚,股东? - 不相信他们
- Stocks,shares? - Doesn't trust them.
一朝被蛇咬,十年怕井绳 发誓再也不会相信了
Dabbled once,lost heavily.Vowed never again.
这家伙斤斤计较,一毛不拔
The man's a block of ice.He calculates the odds.
他永远不会担一点风险
He never goes out on a limb.
至少我所能看见的他唯一 热爱的事情,就是极端地暴力
The only thing he's passionate about,as far as I can see,is extreme violence.
有一件事情
There is one thing.
他总是随身携带笔记本电脑
He carries a laptop wherever he goes.
如果他有弱点的话,这是我们唯一 可以从中发现的地方
If he has got a weakness,that's where we'll find it.
很好,能给Danny一个机会来向我们 展示他学到了多少
Good,it'll give Danny a chance to show us how much he's learned.
我们怎么做?
How we doing?
就看我们花在布局上的精力和时间了
Depends how much we spend on the set up.
不管怎么样,他都惹到了Albert
Whatever it takes.He put his hands on Albert.
但我在书上看到说 "永远不要让你的情感控制理智"
But I thought the book says,"Never let your heart rule your head."
你好?
Hello?
你妻子
Your wife.
我觉得没用
I don't think it works.
什么?
What?
从硬盘上下载下来的东西中进行感应
Downloading from the hard disk telepathically.
- 我还在想 - 但他们已经在吃甜点了
- I'm thinking. - But they're on dessert.
各个击破
Divide and conquer.
打搅一下,你丢了把叉子
Excuse me,you dropped a fork there.
好玩吗?
Having fun?
会让你自然放松
That's a natural laxative.
- 什么?眼药水? - 是的,就看着吧
- What?Eye drops? - Yeah,just watch.
- 我以为你不能忍受这个地方 - 我不能
- I thought you couldn't stand this place. - I can't.
那这一定非常重要
Then it must be important.
Stacie告诉过你我来看你了吗?
Did Stacie tell you I came to see you?
- 她为什么不呢? - 你没有打电话
- Why wouldn't she? - You didn't call.
我很忙的
I've been busy.
- 你看起来不错 - 是不错
- You look well. - I am.
- 谢谢你的信 - 我没有什么好说的
- Thanks for the letters. - I had nothing to say.
我要离婚.没什么的
I want a divorce.Nothing else.
表格只需要一个签名 我曾经邮寄过给你
The forms just need a signature.I even put a stamp on for you.
Simon和我要结婚了
Simon and I want to get married.
那么?
Well?
我这么快就从一个配偶变成了 一个障碍,我觉得我都快喷血了
I've gone from soul mate to obstacle so fast,I think I'm gonna get a nosebleed.
你总是爱这个胜过我
You always loved this more than me.
你曾经所梦想过的,就是他了吗?
Everything you ever dreamed of,is he?
只要在纸上签个字,Mick
Just sign the papers,Mick.
2分钟
Two minutes.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
快点
Come on.
过来了
Nearly there.
快点!
Come on!
好了,Dan
Got it,Dan.
好了,现在
Well,now.
- 一直就明摆在那里的 - 和往常一样
- It was there all the time. - The usual.
我只是没有意识到
I just didn't see it.
这家伙对电影很狂热
This guy is crazy about the movies.
他很浪漫,特别是对于黑白电影
The guy's a romantic,so strictly black and white.
Stacie需要比Diaz更为经典
Then Stacie needs to be classier than Diaz.
就像赫本那样的
Someone classic,like Hepburn.
明白了
Got it.
Mickey
Mickey.
听着,我们谈过了我的提升问题
Listen,we talked about me moving up.
- 直接参与在下次的大行动中 - 那可是在你搞砸之前
- Working the inside on the next big score. - That was before you screwed up.
是的,完全正确
Yeah,exactly.
我们得让那些人听从Eddie的命令为Albert拉一只队伍
We need to get the lads down to Eddie's.We're putting a team together for Albert.
你不应该拿Danny出气
You shouldn't take it out on Danny.
Pete不错,Sam怎么样?他有空吗?
Pete will be great.What about Sam?Is he free?
帮我打个电话给他好吗?
Give him a call for me,would you?
还有什么你能想到的人吗?
Any other names you can mention who might be about?
Danny,要尽你最大的努力
Danny,knock yourself out.
谢谢,Andy.Albert会非常感激的
Thanks,Andy.Albert will really appreciate it.
- Sam - Monroe小姐
- Sam. - Miss Monroe.
- 你或许需要刮个胡子,Sam - 为了Albert?当然可以
- You might need to shave,Sam. - For Albert?Sure.
- 嗨,美女 - 你好,Pete
- Hi,trinkle. - Hello,Pete.
- 最近怎么样? - 我来这里是为了Albert,是不是?
- How you doing? - I'm here for Albert,all right?
海上图片社?你好
Maritime Pictures?Hello,there.
这周晚些时候我要和你们的财物总监有个会议
I have a meeting with your financial director there later this week.
我有些问题,你能把路线传真给我吗?
I was wondering,could you fax me directions?
好的,亲爱的,非常感谢,再见
Yeah,lovely.Thanks very much.Bye-bye.
好了
Okay.
好了.我们帮你在Gorley的旅馆登记了一间房间...
Right.We've booked you into a room at Gorley's hotel...
里面有从每个主要的好莱坞工作室 给你的传真在等着你
and there are faxes waiting for you from every major Hollywood studio.
我们知道他会监视他所有的客人...
We know he keeps tabs on all his guests...
当然不会拒绝和你这样电影界的大人物碰面的机会
and won't pass up the opportunity to meet a big shot movie mogul like you.
- 你准备好了? - 是的
- You ready? - Yeah.
照约定好的做,Danny
By the book,Danny.
我并不知道其他的方法
I don't know any other way.
看着他的眼睛,像他一样思考
Look into his eyes,and think as he thinks.
为了Albert
For Albert.
好了
Okay.
早上好.我能来为你介绍一项特殊的折扣吗?
Good morning.Could I interest you in a special discount?
早上好
Good morning.
你好.我能来为你介绍一项特殊的折扣吗?
Hello.Could I interest you in a special discount?
我要离婚
I want a divorce.
- 我们都准备好了 - 好的
- We're all set. - Right.
我从来没有见过你的这一面
Well,this is a whole new side of you I haven't seen before.
- 什么? - 在沉默中忍受痛苦
- What? - Suffering in silence.
你为什么觉得我在忍受痛苦?
What makes you think I'm suffering?
因为快乐先生几天前离开了城市
Mr.Happy left town days ago.
- 谢谢你为Danny所做的一切 - 为什么突然那么关心了?
- Thanks for what you're doing for Danny. - Why the sudden interest?
- Albie叫我要留心一下他 - Albie
- Albie told me to look out for him. - Albie.
还有什么Albert不关心的事情吗?
Is there anything Albert hasn't taken care of?
没有
No.
听着,如果沉默对你不再管用...
Listen,if the strong silent thing stops working for you...
- 而你想找人来聊聊的话... - 没事
- and you need somebody to talk to... - Yeah.
是Rachel
It's Rachel.
- 她要离婚 - 然后?
- She wants a divorce. - And?
- 就这样 - 你同意了?
- And that's it. - So you agreed?
我告诉她我要想一想
I told her I'd think about it.
- 怎么了?没有什么训话吗?? - 你有这方面所有的才能
- What?No lecture? - You've got all this talent.
你能让人们按照你的意志来屈服 让他们做你想做的
You can bend people to your will.Make them do what you want them to.
如果你下决心做...
If you set your mind to it...
你可以在一周之内说服她让你回来
you can convince her in a week to take you back.
- 为什么不呢? - 你觉得我应该把Rachel骗回来?
- So why don't you? - You think I should con Rachel back?
那不就是我们做的吗,Mickey?
That's what we do isn't it,Mickey?
创建一个我们想要的那种世界?
Create a world the way we want it to be?
你让她确信你能成为她想要的那种男人
You convince her that you can be the man she wants.
问题是,你先要让你自己信服
Problem is,you gotta convince yourself first.
那么,我们去搞定这个混蛋吧
So,let's go get this bastard.
来本房屋和花园谢谢
House & Garden, please.
影视新闻
Movie News.
Harris先生,我是医院管理中心的
Mr.Harris,I'm from the hospital administration.
我们需要讨论一下你要如何支付你的账户
We need to talk about how you'd like to settle your account.
我希望你去和其他人说吧,你个笨蛋
I wish you lot would talk to each other.You're a mess.
- 不好意思? - 我已经付了我的钱,用现金
- I'm sorry? - I've already settled my account.Cash.
特殊折扣
The special discount.
- 我们收到了给你的一些传真,Elliott先生 - 是吗?
- We've had some faxes for you,Mr.Elliott. - Yeah?
这些电影工作室.他们永远不会让我闲着
These movie studios.They never leave me alone.
帮我个忙好吗,亲爱的?
Wanna do me a favor,sweetheart?
给我送点矿泉水和新鲜的水果上来
Send me up some mineral water and some fresh fruit.
当然可以,先生
Of course,sir.
车在外面
The car's outside.
我会负责的,祝你在这里住得愉快
I'll see to it,and I hope you enjoy your stay.
是啊,我相信会的,谢谢
Yeah,I'm sure I will.Thank you.
按照约定的来,Danny
By the book,Danny.
Jason Elliott
Jason Elliott.
- 你在做电影方面的业务? - 他们是这么说的
- So you're in the film business? - So they tell me.
你喜欢电影,Frank?
You like the movies,Frank?
打我还是个孩子的时候起
Since I was a kid.
他们可不像看起来那样在制作电影
They don't make them like they used to.
你到底是做什么的呢?
So,what is it you do exactly?
我找到钱并让魔法发生
I find the money that makes the magic happen.
你想过把钱投到电影中来吗,Frank?
You ever thought of putting money into films,Frank?
- 我喜欢看到钱在哪里 - 那是哪里?
- I like my money where it is. - And where is that?
我可以看得见的地方
Where I can see it.
- 抱歉离开一会儿 - 当然
- Would you excuse me? - Sure.
嘿,Frank
Hey,Frank.
我稍后要和两个投资者一起吃饭喝酒
I'm wining and dining a couple of investors later.
或许在这里度过一晚,可以吗?
Might be nice to round the night off here,if that's okay?
- 没问题 - 谢谢,Frank,非常感谢
- No problem. - Thanks,Frank,I appreciate that.
Danny认为我们需要2万英镑才能使他信服
Danny thinks we need 20,000 for the convincer.
我们还缺多少?
How much are we short?
如果我们预先可以从Gorley那里拿到4000镑
If we can get 4,000 from Gorley up front,
我们可以凑齐16000镑
we can scrape 16,000.
我告诉你们,Gorley那里机关重重
I'm telling you,Gorley's got trouble written all over him.
我只是不想准备不充分得到那里
I just don't want to get in there and be half-cocked.
那么问题就是:
So the question is:
今天晚上这个时候我们要去哪里弄他妈的4000镑?
Where are we going to find a sucker with 4,000 at this time of the night?
什么?不
What?No.
拜托,Eddie.这可比银行要好 3天有50%的回报
Come on,Eddie.It's better than the banks.A 50% Return in three days.
不
No.
- 为了Albert - 不
- It's for Albert. - No.
- 你可不可以不要再说"不"? - 不
- Will you stop saying "no"? - No.
Albert告诉我如果我觉得在和骗子说话...
Albert told me that if I ever thought I was talking to a con man...
就一直说不
just keep saying no.
我们不是要骗你,Eddie,我们是在找你帮忙
We're not trying to con you,Eddie,we're asking for your help.
- 3天? - 最多
- Three days? - Tops.
- 为了Albert? - 绝对
- For Albert? - Absolutely.
如果我没有拿回我的钱,你们就都被我隔绝了
If I don't get paid back,you're all barred.
很高兴见到你
Good seeing you.
- 怎么样? - 很好
- How you doing? - Okay.
- 我们在这里干嘛? - 来吧,放松点
- What are we doing here? - Come on,just relax.
Frank,这是Jeff Machin
Frank,this is Jeff Machin.
Jeff,这是Frank Gorley.他掌管这个地方
Jeff,this is Frank Gorley.He owns this place.
傲慢的家伙
Arrogant asshole.
- 他有什么问题? - 你告诉我吧
- What's his problem? - You tell me.
去年我帮这个家伙赚了3百万美元...
I made the guy $3 million last year...
而他对我就像是雇佣来的一样
he treats me like the hired help.
不好意思,Frank
Excuse me,Frank.
- 这些混蛋在骗我 - Joe,冷静下来,好吗?
- These bastards are cheating on me. - Joe,just calm down,okay?
我给你弄点咖啡
Let's get you a coffee.
我不要咖啡,我要再来一杯 你们这帮骗人的混蛋!
I don't want a coffee,I want another drink.You cheating bastards!
对不起,Frank.没事的
I'm sorry,Frank.It's okay.
- 你的朋友需要上堂礼仪课 - 我知道
- Your friend needs a lesson in manners. - I know.
你这里有谁可以把他送回家的吗?
You got somebody who can maybe run him home?
什么?
What?
Joe或许不喜欢输钱 但他有很强的关系
Joe might not like to lose his money,but he's got very powerful connections.
他是史泰龙的一个私交
He's a personal friend of Sly Stallone.
我答应我会看着他的
And I promised that I'd keep an eye on him.
他认识史泰龙?
He knows Sly Stallone?
也不是很认识他,更熟悉他的妈妈
Well,it's not so much Sly,it's more his mother.
- 我可以买下这个地方 - 他住在Grovesnor
- I could buy this place. - He's staying at the Grovesnor.
把这里关掉吧,把它变成一堆屎
Close it down,turn it into a shithole.
对不起,Frank.我要跟Jeff谈谈
I'm sorry,Frank.I gotta talk to Jeff.
你有什么安静点的地方吗?
You got anywhere quiet?
- 有 - 谢谢
- Yeah. - Thank you.
他是个醉鬼.我不要和他一起工作
He's a drunk.I don't want to work with him.
来吧,Joe没事的
Come on,Joe's okay.
如果这次他在其中,那就不要算我
If he's in this time,then count me out.
- 我向你保证 - 那你们两个都走开
- I gave you my word. - Then screw him and screw you.
和你一起做生意的人可是有 很严重的态度问题啊
The people you do business with have got a really bad attitude problem.
你知道吗?
You know that?
帮我个忙,朋友?
Do me a favor,pal?
少管和你无关的事
Keep your nose out of what doesn't concern you.
好了,够了
Okay,that's enough.
你要管好你的嘴,孩子
You want to watch your mouth,boy.
对不起,Frank,Jeff只是很讨厌Joe
I'm sorry,Frank,Jeff's just wound up about Joe.
好吧,好吧,不带他了
Okay,look.All right.He's out.
那我要找其他人来帮他收尾
I'll get somebody else to cover his end.
这里是Frank的办公室...
Now,this is Frank's office...
还是要有些尊重的
a bit of respect wouldn't go amiss.
- 你找到买主了吗? - 都会安排妥当的
- You found a buyer yet? - It's all in place.
我们在15000镑的时候买进 等到60000的时候再出来
We buy in at 15,000,we get back 60,000.
这就是电影的特殊之处
That's film extras.
在所有的演员中介里面 他们试图对每个带有...
In all the casting agencies,they try and strike up an exclusive...
强大预算的电影构造一个专有权
with any movie with a decent budget.
这只是盛大安排中的一个小土豆...
It's small potatoes in the grand scheme of things...
但是,嘿,每一点都是要计算的,不是吗?
but,hey,every little counts,right?
除了我们刚失去了Joe
Except we just lost Joe.
- 我说了,我会来操心的 - 怎么弄?
- I said,I'd take care of it. - How?
这是桩现金交易.我们可是要在早餐的时候 和制片人见面的...
This is a cash deal.We meet the producer at breakfast...
而那是银行还没有开门
before the banks open.
你知道吗?
You know what?
话说回来,我很高兴Joe已经出局了
Screw the deal,I'm glad Joe's out of it.
这个家伙只对净赚的有兴趣 他什么都不懂
The guy's only interested in the bottom line.He's got no soul.
你知道他最喜欢的电影是什么吗,Frank?兰博
You know what his favorite film is,Frank?Rambo.
你怎么会和这样的家伙做生意的呢?
How are you gonna do business with a guy like that?
- Bogart,Cagney,他们才是演电影的 - 你喜欢Cagney?
- Bogart,Cagney,now they made movies. - You like Cagney?
他真是前无古人,后无来者
No one like him,before or since.
- 最好的电影?- 白热杀机
- Best film?- White Heat.
- "成了!妈!" - "世界之巅"
- "Made it,Ma." - "Top of the world."
好电影,但不是他最好的 你知道他曾经是个舞者么?
Good film,but not his best.Do you know he was a dancer?
- 在电影中穿插舞蹈? - 是的
- Came up through vaudeville? - That's right.
电影中最好的歌者和舞者
Best song and dance man in the business.
你们两个讨论结束的话,我们是否能回到手头的正事上来?
When you two have finished,can we get back to the job in hand?
可以
Yeah.
到底是什么问题?
So what is this deal exactly?
是和制作人的问题,额外的合同
The deal is with the producer,for the extras contract.
我们和他见面,付清他的钱 然后去片场...
We meet him,pay him off,then go to the set...
从中介那家伙处去搜集钱
and collect from the guy from the agency.
- 片场? - 是的
- A film set? - Yeah.
问题是,就像Jeff说的,我们少了Joe 所以缺了5000镑
Trouble is,like Jeff says,we lost Joe so we're 5,000 light.
我直说吧
Let me get this straight.
你们给这个制片人15000镑...
You take this producer 15,000...
然后就开车到片场去搜集60000镑?
then you drive over to the film set and collect 60,000?
差不多就是这个意思
That's about the strength of it.
如果我提供了你们缺的5000镑呢?
So what if I put up the 5,000 you're light?
只要我提供了Joe这个家伙的份 那他的那份回报也就给我
So long as I pick up his share,this guy Joe's share,in return.
- 没门 - 我没有在和你说
- No way. - I wasn't talking to you.
你要让这个家伙硬挤进来吗?
You gonna let this guy muscle in?
他所做的只是接管Joe的部分 那又有什么区别呢?
All he'd be doing is taking over Joe's share.What difference does it make?
我都不认识这个家伙
I don't even know this guy.
看在上帝的份上,这个猪头现在要给我们支票啊
For God's sake,the lame brain's gonna give us a check now.
- Jeff,拜托,求你了.放松点 - 好吧
- Jeff,come on,please.Just relax. - All right.
必须是要现金的,Frank.对不起
It does have to be cash,Frank.I'm sorry.
你可不可以礼貌一些?
You gonna be polite?
Frank帮我们脱离Joe呢 至少我们可以让他插进来吧
Frank helped us out with Joe.Cutting him in is the least we can do.
谢谢,Frank
Thanks,Frank.
就像我说的,我喜欢钱在我能看见的地方
Like I said,I like my money where I can see it.
我和你们一起去
I'm coming with you.
好的
All right.
我要叫了
I'll call.
3个7
Three sevens.
同花
Flush.
再来
Again.
- Pete - 你倒是很及时嘛
- Pete. - You took your time.
很高兴见到你
Nice to see you,too.
钱在那个口开着的袋子里面 先把那个给Danny
The money's in the one with the flap open,so give that one to Danny first.
- 什么时候? - 尽快吧
- How long? - Any minute now.
记住不要让别人看见
Just be out of sight.
我告诉过你了,Lucy 不拿开那条绳子我就走
I've told you,Lucy,either the line goes or I do.
哦,耶酥基督,去告诉他们!
Well,Jesus Christ!Go and tell them.
- Jenny亲爱的 - Jason
- Jenny baby. - Jason.
怎么样了?
How's it going?
导演是个蠢蛋 你能帮我开了他吗?
The director's a moron.Can't you fire him for me?
亲爱的,我可以.但他会让我先滚蛋
Baby,I could,but he'd sue my ass off.
这是我的一个很好的朋友,这是Frank Gorley
This is a very good friend of mine.This is Frank Gorley.
- 很高兴见到你,Frank - 你好?
- Glad to meet you,Frank. - How do you do?
好了,来吧,现在,回去工作 时间就是金钱
Okay,come on,now.Back to work.Time is money.
他真是个苛刻的老板
He's such a slave driver.
- 那是Jenny Cole? - 你认识她?
- That's Jenny Cole? - You know her?
- 我今天早上看到她的新闻 - 她会成为巨星的
- I was reading about her this morning. - She's gonna be huge.
他们把她称为奥黛丽・赫本第二
They're calling her the new Audrey Hepburn.
- Jason - 你好吗?
- Jason. - How you doing?
不错.交易还算数?
Okay.We still on?
已经搞定了
It's a done deal.
很好,我有200个超级崇拜的小明星 真等着点头呢,拿着
Great,I've got 200 wannabe starlets waiting for the nod,here.
- 你们要来帮我选吗? - 不,我们委托你了,好吗?
- You fellas wanna help me pick? - No,we'll leave that,all right?
你是准备说上一整天还是就把我的钱给我?
You gonna talk all day or you gonna give me my money?
就像他说的,分成3份了
Split three ways,just like he said.
漂亮
That's beautiful.
20,000.一个半小时的回馈,不错吧
20,000.Not a bad return for half an hour,is it?
- 看起来Joe的损失是我的获利嘛 - 我想是的
- Looks like Joe's loss is my gain. - I guess so.
既然我们都到了这里
While we're here,
何不逛逛这个片场,看看是如何拍电影的呢?
any chance of walking around the set,watching a bit of filming?
Frank,我要回去了.要去摆平Joe
Frank,I gotta get back.Square things up with Joe.
我以为Joe已经不再参与了呢
I thought Joe was out of the picture.
他还在里面,在做笔大生意
He is for this but not the big one.
- 大生意? - 闭嘴,Jason
- Big one? - Shut your mouth,Jason.
- 我说什么了吗? - 上车吧
- Did I say anything? - Just get in the car.
有谁问起我的话,就告诉他们我5分钟之前离开了
Anybody asks for me,tell them I left five minutes ago.
我的4000镑在哪里?
So where's my 4,000?
我们送出去了
We just gave it away.
嗨,Eddie
Hi,Eddie.
- 你们就把我的钱送出去了? - 是的
- Did you just give my money away? - It's all right.
- 是个诱饵 - 诱饵?
- It was bait. - Bait?
我们一切还顺利吧?
So did we get the green light?
我们今晚会和他摊牌
We tell him the tale tonight.
- 他来了.Frank.你好吧? - 很好
- Here he is.Frank.How are you doing? - Okay.
- 你还记得Jenny吗? - 当然
- You remember Jenny? - Of course.
她今天拍晚了.想要一些休息和放松
She wrapped late today.She wants a little bit of R and R.
不好意思.你是Jennifer Cole?
Excuse me.Are you Jennifer Cole?
你有笔吗?
Have you got a pen?
谢谢
Thank you.
你能在Jen玩牌的时候找个人看着她吗?
Can you get someone to watch over Jen while she plays the tables?
没问题
No problem.
不要让Cole小姐受到打扰
See Miss Cole isn't bothered.
- 好好玩吧 - 谢谢,Frank
- Go have fun. - Thank you,Frank.
- 我们能喝一杯吗? - 当然
- Can we get a drink? - Yeah.
Joe怎么样了?
How did it go with Joe?
- 这个家伙是个蠢蛋 - 我6个月前就告诉你了
- The guy's a fruit loop. - I told you that six months ago.
真是羞愧啊,我还有些喜欢他呢,你知道吗?
It's a shame,I kind of liked him,you know?
- 但这可是在做买卖 - 是是是
- But this is business. - Yeah.
那那个大生意是什么东西?
So what about the big one?
- 你之前有提起过 - Jeff?
- You mentioned it earlier. - Jeff?
好了,Frank,坐下
Okay,Frank,sit down.
告诉他吧
Tell him.
我们准备要制作部电影 低成本的.大概是5百万英镑
We're gonna make a movie.Kind of low budget.Say about 5,000,000.
而Jenny觉得现在是她转型的时候...
Jenny thinks it's her big break in the States...
但我们真正想在亚洲赚钱
but where we're really gonna make our money is in Asia.
亚洲?
Asia?
- 我能坦白讲吗,Frank? - 请
- Can I be frank,Frank? - Please.
在其他的人正盯着家庭市场的时候...
While everyone else is looking at the home market...
我们先把影片直接卖给亚洲
we sell the video rights to Asia up front.
我们可以直接给出价钱
We can virtually name our price.
那样我们可以不费吹灰之力就能赚到1千万英镑
I figure we're gonna get 10 million without breaking a sweat.
- 她同意那么做? - 她昨天已经签订合同了
- And she's agreed to do it? - She signed the contract yesterday.
Joe在里面还是不在?
So is Joe in or out?
他还想进来,但你知道这些乌合之众是如何的
He still wants in,but you know what these Mob guys are like.
他们还是有点钱的
They're a liability.
这是净赚的,Frank:
Bottom line is,Frank:
如果你想分一羹的话 我可以帮你
If you want a slice of the cake,I can make it happen.
我们要投入多少钱?
How much are we talking about?
你要投入的跟我和Jeff一样多
It's gonna be the same as me and Jeff are in for.
20万左右吧
That's 200 big ones.
20万英镑?
200,000?
而保证是...
With a guarantee...
你可以在3个月之内收回双倍的回馈
that you're gonna get double your money back in three months.
不,我觉得我还是不要了
No,I think I'll pass.
什么?
What?
我最多出到15000镑,再多我就退出了
I'm 15,000 up.I think I'll quit while I'm ahead.
- 如果我们... - 我们可以找到别人的
- What if we... - We can find someone else.
这不是问题,好吗?
It's not a problem,okay?
- 我们刚才要的酒呢? - 当然
- How about that drink? - Sure.
你要认识到一件事情,Dan
You've got to pick it up,Dan.
你在跟这个家伙谈钱
You're talking to this guy about money.
他被钱所包围,而不是被钱困扰
He's surrounded by money,he's not fazed by it.
你给他的是一些他已经有的东西
You're offering him something he's already got.
你要想想什么能带给我们比钱更多的
You've gotta think about what brought us this far.
你能不能给他一些他从其他地方 所得不到的东西?
What can you give him that he can't get anywhere else?
不要跟他的头脑说话,要跟他的心去说 是情感而不是理智
Don't talk to his head,talk to his heart.Emotion not reason.
想想吧
Think.
- 你喜欢电影,Frank? - 打我还是个孩子时起
- You like the movies,Frank? - Since I was a kid.
- 你喜欢Cagney? - 当然
- You like Cagney? - Of course.
电影中最好的歌者和舞者
Best song and dance man in the business.
你喜欢Cagney?
You like Cagney?
- 你说什么,Frank? - 把我算进去
- What do you say,Frank? - Count me in.
- 这是银行本票 - 谢谢,Frank
- Bankers draft. - Thanks,Frank.
太好了
Now that's beautiful.
这是20万的收据和合同副本
There's a receipt for 200,000 and a copy of the contract.
我们要赚大钱了
We're all going to make a lot of money.
我们会更好的
We'd better.
- 世界之颠 - 世界之颠,Frank
- Top of the world. - Top of the world,Frank.
你不加入我们吗,亲爱的?
You're not gonna join us,baby?
我让这该死的剧本弄得头都大了
I'm trying to get my head around this damn script.
你要我帮你对这些台词吗?
Do you want me to run some lines with you?
你介意吗?
Would you mind?
我告诉你吧,为什么不让Frank帮你呢?
I tell you what.Why doesn't Frank help you?
让他尝试一下新的事物.Frank?
Get him in the swing of things.Frank?
我?
Me?
来吧.你只要跟着脚本和Jen对戏就行了
Come on.You just gotta read through the script with Jen.
你会很棒的,来吧
You're gonna be great.Come on.
去吧
Go ahead.
- 我以前从来没有做过这种事情 - 不要担心,你会很不错的
- I've never done this sort of thing before. - Don't worry you'll be fine.
谢谢,Frank
Thank you,Frank.
谢谢
Thank you.
支票检查过了
Check's cleared.
现在正在转移
It's being transferred now.
是时候保证他不会追着我们了
Time to make sure he won't come after us.
我们今天晚上就搞定他
Then we blow him out tonight.
准备好了?
You ready?
好了
Yeah.
你觉得他没问题吗?
Do you think he's gonna be all right?
如果像他所说的,他会没问题的
If he does as he's told,he'll be fine.
在Mickey开枪或者信号不起作用的时候 你必须面对着他
You have to be face-on to Mickey when he shoots or the signal might not work.
如果不管用,你就捂住胸口倒下
If it doesn't work,when you go down fall on your chest.
努力让血袋破裂,好吗?
The force should split the bag,all right?
Danny,不要演戏,好吗?
Danny,no theatrics,okay?
一枪过后,你就像袋土豆一样的倒下
One shot and you go down like a sack of potatoes.
- 根据约定来做 - 根据约定来做
- By the book. - By the book.
我们好了
We're done.
好了,我们下个月开始出击
Okay,we start shooting next month.
Jason整个星期都在和导演讨论
Jason is talking to directors all week.
我希望他能找到比上一个更好的人
I hope he's getting someone better than the last one.
Jason在哪里?他现在应该在这里
Where is Jason?He should be here by now.
放松点,Frank,他正穿过...
Relax,Frank,he's just crossing the "T's"...
嘿,Jason
Hey,Jason.
- Jason? - 我们惨了
- Jason? - We're screwed.
- 什么? - Joe跑了
- What? - Joe's gone.
- 他第一件事情就是结账离开了旅馆 - 有什么问题吗?
- He checked out of the hotel first thing. - So what's the problem?
他不会再现身了
He wasn't in the picture anyway.
他在银行有联合签名 我还没有来得及去修改
He was co-signature at the bank.I didn't have time to change it.
他在离开之前将我们一扫而空
He cleaned us out before he left.
怎么样一扫而空,扫空了什么?
Cleaned us out how?Of what?
所有的,好吧.所有的都没有了!连一便士都没剩!
Everything,all right.It's all gone!Every penny!
- 上帝,我可有20万在里面! - 是啊,我们都是!
- God,I had 200,000 in there! - Well,we all did!
你是说,他拿走了所有的钱?
You mean,he took all the money?
他也拿走了我的钱
He took my money,too.
我把钱给了你,你个垃圾
I gave that money to you,you little shit.
那我告诉你,都没了!
Well,I'm telling you,it's all gone!
- 那就去拿回来! - 我不能!
- Go get it back! - I can't!
他认为在我们先把他排除在外时 我们就他在躲避他
He figures we welched on him first when we cut him out.
让我知道他去哪里了,我去把钱拿回来
Let me know where he is and I'll get it back.
你不能,我们谁都不能
You can't,none of us can.
他消失了
He's connected.
- 我要要回我的钱 - 不要傻了,Jeff
- I want my money back. - Don't be stupid,Jeff.
拜托,伙计.我告诉你了
Come on,man.I'm telling you.
我告诉你了,他拿走了所有的钱 没有剩下任何东西!
I'm telling you,man,he's taken all of it!There's nothing left!
- Frank. - 你个卑鄙的小人!
- Frank. - You dirty rat!
- 给我出去吧,Frank - 跟她出去!
- Get me out of here,Frank. - Get her out!
Frank,求你了.放松
Frank,please.The press.
- 他弄丢了我的钱! - 求你了,Frank.就算帮我!
- He lost my money! - Please,Frank.Help me!
跟她出去.没事的 我来处理.走
Get her out.It's okay.I'll take care of it.Go.
来吧.不要死在我面前
Come on.Don't die on me.
拜托,Danny.你会好起来的
Come on,Danny.You're gonna be all right.
他怎么样了?
How's he doing?
他们正在给他做手术 Gorley怎么样了?
They're operating on him now.What about Gorley?
他躲起来了.他以为自己杀死了Danny 所以就躲起来了
He's laying low.He thinks he killed Danny,so he'll stay that way.
很好
Good.
- 那警察呢? - 我告诉他们我们找到他的时候就是那样了
- Police? - I told them we found him like that.
他在那里赢了钱然后就被抢劫了
He was there for a big game and got robbed for his stash.
那他们买账吗?
Did they buy it?
没有其他证人,所以他们没有选择
There were no other witnesses,so they had no choice.
- 对不起 - 为什么?
- I'm sorry. - For what?
你是对的,他还没有准备好
You were right.He wasn't ready.
他准备好了,他做的很好
Yes,he was.He did good.
他会好起来的
He's gonna be okay.
3,900.4,000.
- 还有呢? - 利息呢?
- What? - Interest?
- 我以为你们把我忘了呢 - 没呢
- I thought you'd forgotten me. - No.
- 你感觉如何? - 就像是我被射中了
- How do you feel? - Like I've been shot.
医生说你应该很快就可以 起床走动了
The doctor says you should be up and about in no time.
我们有送给Albie的礼物 你要来看看吗?
We've got Albie's present,you want to come?
是啊,我不会错过的
Yeah,I wouldn't miss it for the world.
你的马车准备好了,先生
Your carriage awaits,sir.
- 你们知道我有多讨厌惊喜 - 你会喜欢这个的
- You know how I hate surprises. - You'll like this one.
看看你们两个
Just look at you two.
我应该考虑医疗保险了
I should start taking out medical insurance.
首先,是这个
First,there's this.
嗯,不少钱啊
Well,that's a lot of money.
而现在,则是画龙点睛来了
And now,for the cherry on top.
瞧,Albert...
Look,Albert...
我不知道该怎么道歉才足够
there's no way I can apologize enough.
事实是,我是个白痴
The truth is,I'm an idiot.
我连帮你擦鞋都不够格
I'm not fit to lace your boots.
我就是你鞋子上的屎...
I'm the shit on your shoes...
我不值得你来原谅
and I don't deserve your forgiveness.
但我还是请求你
But I'm begging you.
原谅我
Forgive me.
谢谢你,Frank.你能和我一起对剧本真是太好了
Thank you,Frank.So sweet of you to run those lines with me.
这才是电影艺术
Now that's show biz.